Starting a dream job in a new city, winning a place at a prestigious university abroad or being able to travel for an extended period.
在新城市开始一份理想工作，赢得国外知名大学的一席之地，或者能够进行长时间的旅行。
All fantastic opportunities, but they can leave us feeling sad and alone.
这些都是绝佳的机会，但它们也会让我们感到悲伤和孤独。
What is homesickness and what can we do about it?
什么是思乡病？我们又能做些什么呢？
Homesickness is mentioned in Homer's Odyssey – it's nothing new.
思乡病在荷马的《奥德赛》古诗中就有提及——这并不是什么新鲜事。
Common symptoms include sadness, anxiety and irritability.
常见的症状包括悲伤、焦虑和易怒。
It also can trigger self-protection responses causing people to withdraw from activities and become apathetic and unmotivated.
它还会触发自我保护反应，导致人们从活动中退缩，变得冷漠且缺乏动力。
Homesickness can affect anyone, but there are some factors that can make people more resilient when faced by it.
思乡病可能影响任何人，但有一些因素可以使人们在面对它时更有韧性。
Clinical psychologist Christopher Thurber and healthcare professional Edward Walton, tell us that positive previous experiences of being away from home, an optimistic outlook and a settled home background can help people deal better with the condition.
临床心理学家克里斯托弗·瑟伯和医疗保健专业人士爱德华·沃尔顿告诉我们，以往离家在外的积极经历、乐观的心态以及稳定的家庭背景，可以帮助人们更好地应对这种情况。
Homesickness can also be less severe when someone feels in control of their situation, rather than feeling that they have been forced to move.
当一个人感到自己能掌控局面，而不是觉得自己是被迫背井离乡时，思乡病的症状也会减轻。
Regardless of these factors, homesickness does affect most people who move away from home.
无论这些因素如何，思乡病确实会影响大多数远离家乡的人。
Psychologist Nilufar Ahmed recommends that people acknowledge homesickness, accept that it will happen and work through their feelings.
心理学家尼卢法尔·艾哈迈德建议人们承认思乡病，接受它会发生的事实，并努力化解自己的情绪。
Connections are important.
人际关系很重要。
Ahmed suggests people seek to fully involve themselves in their new surroundings, to focus on the positives of their new environment, get to know new people, and keep themselves active.
艾哈迈德建议人们努力让自己完全融入新环境，关注新环境的积极方面，结识新朋友，并让自己保持活跃。
She also suggests maintaining contact with home, through video chats or other means, and also to have reminders of home, such as familiar food.
她还建议通过视频聊天或其他方式与家乡保持联系，并保有一些家乡的念想，比如熟悉的食物。
However, other psychologists, like Thurber and Walton, remind us that it's important that these connections to home do not prevent people taking up new opportunities.
然而，像瑟伯和沃尔顿这样的其他心理学家提醒我们，这些与家乡的联系不要阻碍人们抓住新的机会，这一点很重要。
Some form of homesickness is almost inevitable when we move to a new place.
当我们搬到一个新地方时，某种形式的思乡病几乎是不可避免的。
Understanding that this is the case, and taking small steps to lessen the impact, can help us make the most of new opportunities.
认识到这一点，并采取一些小步骤来减轻其影响，可以帮助我们充分利用新的机会。